xpats.com 2018-04-03

# Privacy policy | The Bulletin

**Privacy Policy**

Data collection, registration and processing

The Mediahuis Group gathers, registers and processes personal data of its customers and users of its services. Certain data must be provided explicitly, for instance for using certain parts of the website, purchasing a product, taking part in a competition, creating an account, etc.

Other data is collected automatically via ‘cookies’ and other data collecting systems/applications (such as IP address; site use; browser type and language, etc.).

The data provided explicitly or automatically is included and processed in the database of **NV Mediahuis, 2 Katwilgweg, 2050 Antwerp, VAT no. BE 0439.849.666**. NV Mediahuis is responsible for processing the personal data gathered via the website and/or other channels and checks any processing carried out by other parties at its request.

The data automatically becomes accessible to other companies in the Mediahuis Group also (see summary).

** ** **Use of your data**

You guarantee that the data you provide is accurate and complete. If you provide inaccurate data or data belonging to third parties, you may be denied access in full or in part, temporarily or permanently, to the Mediahuis Group products and services.

Certain applications, such as the digital paper, require your identification prior to their use.  This enables our customer service department to provide support in the event of technical problems and gives the Mediahuis Group insight into your profile and special interests.

We may use your data to contact you directly, by mail, telephone or electronically, such as by e-mail or SMS. In all electronic communication you have the option to unsubscribe from future electronic messages.

With the exception of sensitive information such as political and religious beliefs, your data may be used for selling and promoting products and services and for keeping you informed of offers from the Mediahuis Group – such as editorial initiatives, market studies, promotions, competitions, personalised information and promotional campaigns about products, services, etc. – and its partners.

Personal data such as your name, first name, street, house number, post box number, postal code, place of residence and telephone number may be passed on to other companies if the Mediahuis Group believes they have information that might interest you. Your email address is passed on only with your consent.

The Mediahuis Group companies accept no liability whatsoever for any use made of your data by third parties. The Mediahuis Group websites may contain links to third-party websites or to commercials of third-party advertisers that may collect your personal data. Any such data collection and processing is not the responsibility of Mediahuis Group, but instead of the advertiser or website manager involved.

**Access to and correction of data**

The Mediahuis Group will not keep your data any longer than the statutorily provided terms and in any case not longer than is required for the purposes mentioned herein.

You may obtain access to and make changes to your recorded personal data via your account.

In addition, you may contact us through [privacy@mediahuis.be](mailto:privacy@mediahuis.be) to exercise your right to view, correct, delete and oppose – free of charge – the processing and forwarding of your data.

**Minors**

The Mediahuis Group is mindful of protecting the privacy of minors and encourages parents to take an active part in their children’s online activities.

The Mediahuis Group will never knowingly or intentionally collect the personal data of minors.

The Mediahuis Group encourages minors to inform their parents about their online activities when visiting a Mediahuis Group website and to ask for their parents’ opinions prior to submitting their personal data to the Mediahuis Group.

The Mediahuis Group encourages minors to carefully read its privacy policy together with their parents before creating an account.

We advise minors to use a pseudonym instead of their real name in their email addresses. We also advise minors not to disclose more information than is required for the online use of the services provided by the Mediahuis Group.

Parental consent is also required in the application for subscriptions, products and services offered by the Mediahuis Group via its websites. Subscriptions, products and services are always subject to the Terms and Conditions of the Mediahuis Group.

**General**

The processing of personal data within the Mediahuis Group is governed by Belgian law. Any purchase of our products and/or use of our services – including our websites – implies your agreement to our Privacy Policy, which may be modified from time to time. Any modifications enter into force immediately after publication.
